<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on v2how</title>
    <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on v2how</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://v2how.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Camouflaged Telegram MTProto Proxy Server on Ubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-18-camouflage-telegram-mtproto-proxy-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</author>
      <guid>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-18-camouflage-telegram-mtproto-proxy-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Telegram Messenger supports two kinds of proxies: a standard SOCKS5 proxy server and an MTProto proxy server.
In this post you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to build a camouflaged MTProto proxy server. This style of proxy can help you bypass censorship in certain countries.
By following along, you&amp;rsquo;ll see how to create an Nginx camouflage web server and a hidden MTProto proxy server that implements the fake TLS protocol on the same host as the web server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a V2Ray Tor On-Ramp on Ubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-15-v2ray-tor-on-ramp-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</author>
      <guid>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-15-v2ray-tor-on-ramp-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you in a country where the Tor Project website is blocked, the Tor protocol is blocked, and Tor bridges are also blocked?
If so, this post offers a last resort for situations when all other methods of reaching Tor have failed. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to create a Tor on-ramp on an Ubuntu 20.04 server located outside your country. With this method you can bypass censorship and connect to the Tor network from your existing browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Create an Xray VLESS XTLS Server on Ubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-12-xray-vless-xtls-server-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</author>
      <guid>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-12-xray-vless-xtls-server-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this tutorial you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to install Xray on an Ubuntu 20.04 server.
You&amp;rsquo;ll see how to create a camouflage web server with Nginx, and then you&amp;rsquo;ll see how to install and configure Xray for the VLESS protocol with XTLS security. You&amp;rsquo;ll then test your server with the Qv2ray graphical user interface.
At the end of this tutorial, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a working and tested Xray server.
Prerequisites Before you begin this tutorial, you will need:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
