<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tor on v2how</title>
    <link>https://v2how.github.io/tags/tor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tor on v2how</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://v2how.github.io/tags/tor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Install Tor Browser or Standalone Tor on Ubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-19-tor-browser-standalone-tor-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</author>
      <guid>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-19-tor-browser-standalone-tor-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tor Browser allows users in the non-free world to access the Internet. The standalone Tor program allows volunteers to support this access with relays, bridges, and onion services.
In this post you&amp;rsquo;ll learn four methods for installing on Ubuntu 20.04:
 installing Tor Browser installing standalone Tor from the Ubuntu repositories installing standalone Tor from the Tor Project repositories installing standalone Tor by compiling from source  You do not need to implement all four of these methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a V2Ray Tor On-Ramp on Ubuntu 20.04</title>
      <link>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-15-v2ray-tor-on-ramp-ubuntu-20-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>amyw32@protonmail.com (Amy)</author>
      <guid>https://v2how.github.io/post/2021-02-15-v2ray-tor-on-ramp-ubuntu-20-04/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you in a country where the Tor Project website is blocked, the Tor protocol is blocked, and Tor bridges are also blocked?
If so, this post offers a last resort for situations when all other methods of reaching Tor have failed. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to create a Tor on-ramp on an Ubuntu 20.04 server located outside your country. With this method you can bypass censorship and connect to the Tor network from your existing browser.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
